Guide to the Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, DC records, 1980-2013 MS2230
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Productions, 1980-2007; Series 4
  - Administrative records, 1980-2006; Series 4 Subseries 1
    - Broadcast Music Inc license agreements, 1996-1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Ticket sales research, 1996-2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - DC Commission on Arts and Humanities, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Freedom Festival Gay Pride Day, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Kennedy Center concert, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Presidential inauguration, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Proud & Peaceful production, 1997; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Community Performance, 1997-1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Performances, 1997-1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Rob Neighbor Consulting correspondence, 1997-1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Capital Pride Festival, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Community performances, 1998-1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Holiday concert, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Kennedy Center Millenium Stage, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Merchandise contract, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Nunsense production, 1998-1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Pirates of Penzance, Davina Pons, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Potomac Fever concert, 1998-2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Potomac Fever, 1998-2001; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Rehoboth Beach SCAC concert, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - GALA Choruses Leadership Conference/Singers Weekend, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Holiday concert, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Horsley Memorial, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Little Shop of Horrors, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Pride concert, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Recordings, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Rehearsals, 1999-2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Spring concert, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Ticketmaster ticket sale agreement, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Airways Airforce Trade Program, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Capital Pride Festival, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Community: GMCW, 1999-2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Community performances, 1999-2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Community: Potomac Fever, 1999-2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - United Arts Organization United Way/Combined Federal Campaign, 1999-2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Community and public relations community, 2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Gala Festival, 2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Holiday concerts, 2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Millenium March on Washington gala dinner, 2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Pride concert, 2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Rehoboth Beach, 2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Spring concert, 2000; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - 2000-2001 season, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Community performances, 2000-2001; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Pageant, 2000-2001; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - United Arts Organization, 2000-2001; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - 20th Anniversary events, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - 20th Anniversary concert, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - 20th Anniversary events and publications, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Let Us Entertain You, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Performances publications, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Potomac concert, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Rock Creek Singers, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Spring concerts, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - 2001-2002 season, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Performances, 2001-2002; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Performances, 2001-2002; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - GALA Regional Festival, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Kennedy Center performance, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Performances, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - "Stops Along the Way...A Gay Cabaret", 2002; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - The Wizard of Oz at Lisner Auditorium, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - 2002-2003 Season, Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Changing Hearts voice and piano score, 2004; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Barbara Cook banner CD, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 1 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Programs, 1980-2007; Series 4 Subseries 2
    - Performances programs, 1981-2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Performances programs, 1982-2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Performances programs, 1982-1999; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Performances programs, 1983-1984; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Performances programs, 1985-1986; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Performances programs, 1987-1988; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Chorus Call programs, 1989-1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Performances programs, 1989-1990; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Performances mailers, circa 1990-circa 1999; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Gay Men's Chorus/Federal City Performing Arts Association presents...programs, 1991-1992; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Performances programs, 1991-1995; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - GALA Festival programs, 1992-2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Performances programs, 1992-1999; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Gay Men's Chorus/Federal City Performing Arts Association presents...programs, 1993; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Gay Men's Chorus presents...programs, 1994-1995; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Performances programs, 1996-1997; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Performances programs, 1998; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Performances programs, 1999; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Performances programs, 2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Performances programs, 2000; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Performances programs, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Performances programs, 2001; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Performances programs, 2002; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Performances programs, 2003; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Performances programs, 2004; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Performances programs, 2005; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Performances programs, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Performances programs, 2006; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Performances programs, 2007; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Performances programs, 2007; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Performances posters, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Posters, undated; Series 4 Subseries 2 (Box 52)
- Audiovisual materials, 1986-2007; Series 5
  - Curtain Up! cassettes, 1986; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - GALA choruses Festival II cassettes, 1986; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Brothers in Harmony cassettes, 1988; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Hooray for Hollywood cassettes, 1988; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - My Kind of Town cassettes, 1988; Series 5 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - The Genius of America cassettes, 1989; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Going on the Road cassettes, 1989; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Going on the Road VHS, 1989; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Tidings of Joy - A Holiday Concert VHS, 1990; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Gay Men's Choruses of Boston, Washington, and Denver Symphony Hall, Boston cassettes, 1990; Series 5 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Trio in Harmony Concert VHS, 1991; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Puttin on the Ritz VHS, 1992; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Singing Free CD, 1994; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - In a Festive Time and Place cassettes, 1996; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - In a Festive Time and Place VHS, 1996; Series 5 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Holly Near in Concert! cassettes, 1996; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - At Home: The Holiday Concert VHS, 1997; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - My Buddy: Featuring the DC Premier of Naked Man VHS, 1997; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - No Talent Show - Camp Round Meadow VHS, 1997; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - In Our Lifetime CD, 1998; Series 5 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Let it Shine CD, 1999; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Potomac River CD, 2000; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - And in That Moment: Treasures of the Holiday CD, 2001; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - I Dream of a Tune CD, 2001; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Various Voices CD, 2001; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Love Songs & Other Fairy Tales...A Cabaret CD, 2002; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - The Songs of Sondheim & Hammerstein CD, 2002; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Auction CDs, 2003; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - When Pigs Fly DVD, 2003; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Let Me Be the Music CD, 2004; Series 5 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Changing Hearts CD, 2005; Series 5 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - 25th Anniversary Tribute DVD, 2006; Series 5 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - This House Shall Stand CD, 2007; Series 5 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - An Invitation to Dance! cassettes, undated; Series 5 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Summer Showcase, undated; Series 5 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Photographs, 1984-2004; Series 6
  Identified photographs arranged alphabetically. Most of the images are not yet identified.
  - Chrous Hop photographs, 1984-1990; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Group images, 2000, undated; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - L.A. Hotel Bel [Ayr], undated; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Lincoln Memorial steps, undated; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Stephen Brent Miller memorial service, 2004; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Photograph album, undated; Series 6 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, 1991 August, undated; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, 1991 August, undated; Series 6 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, 1996, undated; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, undated; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, undated; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, undated; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, undated; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, undated; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    On CD.
  - Photographs, undated; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, undated; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, undated; Series 6 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Photograph and memorabilia album [1/5], undated; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Photograph and memorabilia album [2/5], undated; Series 6 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Photograph and memorabilia album [3/5], undated; Series 6 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Photograph and memorabilia album [4/5], undated; Series 6 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Photograph and memorabilia album [5/5], undated; Series 6 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Photograph and memorabilia album [1/6], undated; Series 6 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Photograph and memorabilia album [2/6], undated; Series 6 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Photograph and memorabilia album [3/6], undated; Series 6 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Photograph and memorabilia album [4/6], undated; Series 6 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Photograph and memorabilia album [5/6], undated; Series 6 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Photograph and memorabilia album [6/6], undated; Series 6 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Photographs and negatives, 1991 August, undated; Series 6 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Photographs and negatives, 1998 November; Series 6 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Photographs and negatives, 1998 November; Series 6 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Photographs and negatives, 1998 November, undated; Series 6 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Photographs and negatives, undated; Series 6 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Photographs and negatives, undated; Series 6 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Photographs and negatives, undated; Series 6 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Photographs and negatives, undated; Series 6 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Photographs and negatives, undated; Series 6 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Photographs and negatives, undated; Series 6 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Photographs and negatives, undated; Series 6 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Photographs and negatives, undated; Series 6 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Photographs and negatives, undated; Series 6 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Photographs and negatives, undated; Series 6 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Photographs and negatives, undated; Series 6 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Photographs and negatives, undated; Series 6 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Photographs and negatives, undated; Series 6 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Photographs and negatives, undated; Series 6 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- 2015 donation materials, 1981-2013; MS2230 Series 7
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Gift of Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, DC., June 29, 2015 (2015.037)
  The original order of the 2015 donation has been maintained throughout Series 7 and its subseries. There are some natural chronological or topical groupings from the original order created by the donor organization.
  This series contains financial records, programs, publicity, recordings, posters, articles related to the work of the organization. The material dates from 1981-2013. Please note that for box 8 the folder titles and dates written on the folders are not accurate for the content in the folders. The titles in this finding aid are accurate.
  Materials containing personal information of Chorus members (where the information has not been publically shared previously) have been restricted. For the most part, this includes member rosters/directories cotaining members' full contact information.
  - Governance, 1981-2012; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1
    The materials in this subseries include board meeting minutes, board member documents, organizational planning documents, annual reports, and other administrative records. The material dates from 1981 to 2012.
    For additional Governance-, administrative- and Board-related materials, please see Series 1.
    - Board Handbook, FY2003-2004, 2002-2004; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Board Handbook, FY2011-2012 [and 2011-2014 Strategic Planning Documents], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors Handbook, 1987 [1/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors Handbook, 1987 [2/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Board Folder [containing materials from multiple seasons] [1/2], 2001, 2004-2005, 2009-2010, 2013; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Board Folder [containing materials from multiple seasons] [2/2], 2001, 2004-2005, 2009-2010, 2013; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Organizational Assessment & Audience Development Plan, circa 2004; Series 7 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Executive/Administrative correspondence and miscellaneous documents, 1993-1995, 1999-2001, 2004-2007, 2009, 2013; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Capital Club invitations and GMCW materials, 2002-2004, undated; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Annual Reports, Board Retreats [1/4], 2000-2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, Board Retreats [2/4], 2000-2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, Board Retreats [3/4], 2000-2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, Board Retreats [4/4], 2000-2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Articles of Incorporation (1981); By-Laws 1997, 1981, 1997; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Proposed B-Laws 1997, Tax statements 1999, Articles of Inc. (1981), 1981, 1987, 1996-1999, 2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      Folder title was supplied by the donors, however, the original binder also had a label "Public Documents."
    - Insurance Policies, 1999-2000; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Insurance Policies, 2000-2002; Series 7 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors Meetings/Minutes, 2004-2005 [1/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors Meetings/Minutes, 2004-2005 [2/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, 2005-2006 [1/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, 2005-2006 [2/2], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, 2006-2007, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Insurance Policy & Correspondence, 1998-2002; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Insurance Policy & correspondence [1/2], 2001-2007; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Insurance Policy & correspondence [2/2], 2001-2007; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Board Meetings 2008-2009, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Insurance Policies [1/2], 2003, 2005-2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Insurance Policies [2/2], 2003, 2005-2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Insurance Policy, 2005-2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - GMCW Website, 2004; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - 2000 P St Office Lease, 2004, 2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Board Meetings 06-07 [Strategic Plan Draft and Financial Documents] [1/2], 2005-2007; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Board Meetings 06-07 [Strategic Plan Draft and Financial Documents] [2/2], 2005-2007; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Board materials, roster, minutes, employee handbook, BoD Handbook [Board Meetings 07-08] [1/3], 2004-2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      These folders do not contain a confidential member roster--even though it is mentioned in the folder title supplied by the donor-so no rosters have been restricted following exisiting policy.
    - Board materials, roster, minutes, employee handbook, BoD Handbook [Board Meetings 07-08] [2/3], 2004-2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Board materials, roster, minutes, employee handbook, BoD Handbook [Board Meetings 07-08] [2/3], 2004-2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Board minutes, audit, 2008-2009; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Board retreat, minutes & reports, financial statements, audit [Board Meetings 07/08] [1/4], 2007-2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Board retreat, minutes & reports, financial statements, audit [Board Meetings 07/08] [2/4], 2007-2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Board retreat, minutes & reports, financial statements, audit [Board Meetings 07/08] [3/4], 2007-2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Board retreat, minutes & reports, financial statements, audit [Board Meetings 07/08] [4/4], 2007-2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Board retreat, 2007-2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Board reports, meetings, minutes, 2011-2012; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Board minutes & reports [1/2], 2009-2010; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Board minutes & reports [2/2], 2009-2010; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Board reports, minutes & materials, 2009-2010; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Board selection material [Governing], undated; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Board materials, retreat, minutes & reports, financial statements, budget, Board pledges [1/2], 2011-2012, 2014; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Board materials, retreat, minutes & reports, financial statements, budget, Board pledges [2/2], 2011-2012, 2014; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Financial records, 1987-2000; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2
    This subseries contains tax documents for the Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, DC. The material dates from 1987-2000.
    For other Financial records, see Series 2.
    - Tax Documents [1/3], 1987-1989, 1991, 1994-1995, 1999-2000; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Tax Documents [2/3], 1987-1989, 1991, 1994-1995, 1999-2000; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Tax Documents [3/3], 1987-1989, 1991, 1994-1995, 1999-2000; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - FY03 Audit, 2002-2003; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - FY02 Audit, 2001-2002; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - FY01 Audit, 2000-2001; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - FY00 Audit, 1999-2000; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - FY99 Audit, 1998-1999; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - FY02 Audit, 2001-2002; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - FY09 Audit [FY08 Audit] [1/2], 2008-2009; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - FY09 Audit [FY08 Audit] [2/2], 2008-2009; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - FY07 Audit, 2006-2007; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - FY06 Audit, 2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - FY04 Audit [FY05 Audit], 2004-2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - FY04 Audit, 2004; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Form 990, contracts, proposals, financial statements, 2009 audit [FY10 Audit] [1/4], 2009-2011; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Form 990, contracts, proposals, financial statements, 2009 audit [FY10 Audit] [2/4], 2009-2011; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Form 990, contracts, proposals, financial statements, 2009 audit [FY10 Audit] [3/4], 2009-2011; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Form 990, contracts, proposals, financial statements, 2009 audit [FY10 Audit] [4/4], 2009-2011; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - FY09 Audit, Form 990 [1/2], 2008-2009; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - FY09 Audit, Form 990 [2/2], 2008-2009; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Auditor's report, Form 990 [1/3], 2009-2012; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Auditor's report, Form 990 [2/3], 2009-2012; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Auditor's report, Form 990 [3/3], 2009-2012; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Financial reports & statements, membership feedback surveys, FY10 budget, FY12 audit, 2010-2013; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Marketing, development, and production records, 1984-2004; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3
    - Advertisement and Article clippings, 2010-2011; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 53, Folder 1)